# **GAGIK SIMONYAN**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Hey I'm Gagik, highly accomplished and userfocused Front-end Developer adept in collaborating with UX and design teams to plan the technical writing and execution of functional specifications for websites and applications. Experienced in building multi-platform websites using JS and RWD.





+374 (094) 89-94-95



simonyangagik36@gmail.com



0068, Yerevan, Armenia



gagik-simonyan.netlify.com

#### SKILLS

- Responive Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- Front-End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **SCHOOL UGEEK**

IT education center 2020 - 2021

#### **BACHELOR OF ECONOMY**

Armenian National Agrarian University

2012 - 2018

## LANGUAGE

- English
- Russian
- Armenian

# EXPERIENCE

#### JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Apollo Inc.

2021 - 2022

- Designed and developed a responsive website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap 4.5
- Communication with clients and team across different projects (financial, educational, e-commerce and etc)
- Closely cooperate with the backend team designing architecture solutions
- Mainly coding with Vanilla or React JS, but I'll master any necessary framework

### MARKET DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

Aghajanyan's Company

2017 - 2021

- Develop, present and implement strategies for acquiring new business
- Engaging with existing and potential customers to gain market information and pinpoint opportunities
- Drive initial prospect targets & qualifications and schedule discovery meetings